Oh, when will you come?
Start now...
Somin, I’m sorry.
It was on my father’s cell phone.
based on records
Mother's disappearance
It has been confirmed that it is connected to Ilseongpa.
I don't believe in the justice that the law says
President Kim!
Only through President Kim
You can go to the commander in chief.
But with this woman
Let's approach the Ilseong faction?
Is that possible?
If the other person betrays us with lies
We will also betray our opponents with lies.
I decided to take revenge now
Wi Chang-ok?
Was Park Gye-soon down there?
What do you want from me?
my collection
Put it between your son and me
send it to china
Hey, newbies
we are professionals
With expertise in each position
It's about opening the hearts of customers.
He already earns 3,600
He is looking for you
Ah
Is it useful to be treated like a VIP like that?
Nice to meet you, this is Maseokgu.
What is your intention?
Tell me, what do you want from me
my here
I want to take a place
First, let’s prove it with the rate of return.
Somin, you finally arrived in China.
Okay, let's give it a try.
I'll give it to you
I can give it to you
Try it somewhere
It's 500 million
This is the price of my mother’s life
Here is Wi Chang-ok
Just one thing
It made a whopping 500 million won in sales.
For our new team leader Wi Chang-ok
Let’s have some fun today!
Now drink, drink
hello
This is manager Miyang Kim.
Who are you?
There is this
A very unlucky woman
'Cause I killed it
That woman
The day I entered the call center
The Korean messenger was arrested
Coincidentally, President Kim also disappeared.
With public trust
Learn more about Wi Chang-ok
I just
I thought there was a really interesting fact
What do you think?
A woman named Wi Chang-ok
Is this the same person as Wi Chang-ok?
This is our mascot
It came from my wallet.
Do you two know each other?
I don't know
You don’t know each other?
actor
Even Azumai’s face came to the performance.
Do I really need to know everything?
I'm at work
Gardening is the most annoying thing
Why?
If these are tamed at best,
I don't even know my topic
I'm busy trying to gain size.
Cutting them out one by one
It's so annoying and I'm so annoyed.
In times like this again
It was so thrilling that I couldn’t stop.
Hey, you bastard
when i speak
You said to think first, right?
that is...
When in doubt
Bringing something more certain
Make it a habit, you bastard
Just a piece of ticket
What are you going to do?
Break the flow of this important conversation
You stupid bastard!
Sorry, CEO.
It's my fault
How much did we talk about?
Do you think it's Mason Dudrick?
If you are a Mason
From Macau to Pit Boss
He was a man who made a name for himself.
- For now...
- In the black collar
Not LTM?
I will speak comfortably with my Silmaluda.
LTM went to the abyss without a doubt
What kind of bullshit is that?
Going to hell?
You didn’t know?
This is a well-known rumor
Black collar makes Mason expensive
It's already been a few months since I took it out.
Oh, there was a feeling like that.
There's no way I don't know
It's natural.
Talented people who control the company
The sheep took it away
It will be noticeable in the go-girl business
Where are the idiots?
But as I watched,
This could be an opportunity
I thought there would be
Opportunity?
Even President Ma knows well.
The country that will be junketed in the future
I think it's Singapore
Oh, where is this?
I just look at this business
I invested in Singapore.
I knew the Macau market would turn out like this
to Singapore in advance
They said they were laying the foundation.
to singapore
A Korean company that owns a casino
Do you know where it is?
Operated by Genie Tourism Development
'Genie The Star Resort'
I'm trying to get Mason out of there
It looks like he's really worn out.
So...
Mason to Genie
I'm not saying we should recruit him, now.
Well, I have to say something that makes sense.
Oh, let's see if I can hear it.
What can we do with that big guy?
Even though I don't know about Masonry
I have a close relationship with my right-hand man.
That baby Mason
This is a composite monument that can be held and held like this
This is Eric Choi.
Eric Choi?
Hey, Wi Chang-ok.
How are you?
Almost
You almost forgot your face, right?
Naedu
I thought you were sick
How are you doing?
Is CEO Nui treating you well?
Well, thanks to me
I'm busy going to meetings here and there.
So?
Oh my, it’s a black collar too
I heard you were busy playing at the restaurant.
Ah, what
I'm trying to raise his price
I'm pooping blood
Hey, I don't even need to wear a black collar.
It's nothing to say
I'll give you more money
I heard there’s a place asking you to come too.
There's a lot of money too
Which company?
Hey, Changok, if you say that, will you use it?
It's business
Oh, by the way
Where and what is Chang-ok doing?
my luggage is in china
Yanbian businessman is President Ma.
Have you seen anything?
Oh, really, I'm leaving LTM?
While farting at Chairman Kim
I heard they only use phishing techniques.
What kind of talent does a guy like that have as a businessman?
I am the representative of that ma.
Let's keep talking
Oh my goodness
Oh, if you feel bad
Yes, I will apologize.
Please understand
Oh, honestly
He, under Chairman Kim
Representative Ma
Me under Mason
Aren’t we in the same situation?
With a heart of sympathy
Yes?
- Apology somehow sounds sarcastic.
- Oh, that can't be true.
Hey, I, just like anyone else
You look confident now
Hey, Mason.
He, in Singapore
You know Marine Bay Casino, right?
The executives there
This time, everything will be changed.
Ah
Marine Bay management is changing?
Mason this bastard
at the director's seat
Instead of me, his wife
Looks like I'm going to sit down, haha
This is why these things on the floor
You shouldn't trust it, it's a disaster.
Oh my, you must be so hurt.
Representative Ma, please think about it.
Even if you have been loyal to your superiors for decades,
In the end when it's at a disadvantage
The tail that gets cut first is
It's us, we
Ah, if it's a tail that gets cut off anyway,
You should ask the owner, shouldn't you?
Would you stab your own master in the back?
Well, exactly
At a business level
I mean, I'm going to make a deal.
If someone wants a mason
Are you saying I can pass it on?
Oh, is the deal a big deal?
giving and receiving
If the needs fit well,
A deal is a deal made.
Write, we
I think the conversation will go quite well.
meet in person
I'd like to talk about it
um
I am
I really like someone who matches well with me.
Well, is there any reason to refuse?
Well, then
I'll send you the location
Once in Korea...
I guess
Making money in China
It's not easy to leave
As you know
They just use phishing techniques.
Aren’t you a person who lives?
If you come, I will treat you with kindness.
child, instead
Do I have to pay for the ticket?
Oh my, that’s how I treat guests.
Take things for granted
The time and date
Let us catch it for you.
This bastard, this, this
I thought it wouldn't come down easily
Magic stone sphere
We need to lure them to Korea quickly.
Whatever I do or say, I do it.
Should I go?
I have to go
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
I received a call from the CEO instead.
Why are you answering the phone now?
Where is Seok-gu going?
Change it right now
sorry
The representative is now in the meeting.
business ledger
- Why is there no news yet?
- I understand you are guessing now.
Immediately at 3 o'clock tomorrow with the LTM agency
I decided to sign a contract
- What do you mean by not sending it to another employee?
- I'm sorry.
I will deliver it immediately
Representative Ma
What meeting are you having now?
This is a script development meeting.
It's a script development meeting.
You say I am now
Looks like you'll believe that
In a situation where you can get in trouble
Are you just sitting there leisurely?
That doesn't make sense
Well, ah, that...
Seokguga
Are you secretly using tricks behind my back?
About this incident?
Absolutely not, Mr. Chairman.
Just a new business...
Yeah?
without my consent
Are you thinking of starting a new business?
Oh, that's not it
Tell it to CEO Ma
Borrowed name account with slush funds
Let's pass it together
To a guy who has other business ideas
I can't trust you with my money
Anyway, you probably know that
Make sure I convey my words well
Chairman, Chairman...
The things below
It looks like it's causing a headache.
This is why people
It's a matter of honor
look at me
At best, he's just a businessman.
Aren’t the things below constantly causing trouble?
That's me
The guy who has one son is just upset.
I can't say anything
Someday, parents' hearts
The day will come when you will know
Is that so?
Anyway
My son suffered from this incident.
It's a disservice to the Chairman.
there will be no more
Ah, Wi Chang-ok.
Is your beauty still the same?
Nin, how did you get old?
I guess I'm getting older on my own
Oh, I
What should I call you?
Oh, look at my mind
Just relax
Please call me Eric.
- here
- Ah
Hey, Surveillance Manager.
Ah, I went to the control tower.
I don't know who is active.
He seems like a person shrouded in a veil.
What do I do if I reveal it?
this handsome face
It's just exposed to the outside world.
Oh, is that so?
Actually in LTM
I've passed by Mason a few times.
So
Even the kids I took with me
I almost saw it all
But it’s Eric’s first time meeting me.
I was curious what kind of person it was.
Oh, what kind of business am I
I thought you wanted to talk
I came a month later
The CEO just said
I guess you were curious?
Oh, even if we do business together
It's time to get to know each other
You need it, right?
Oh, is a Mason otherwise a Mason?
However, on the casino side
I'm the guy who understands
That Yankee guy
There is an Asian man who is in control.
How curious and fun is this?
Not only do I have this face
He is an interesting person in many ways.
But you showed up like this
As if I had been waiting for it
Baby, first time
Is it okay to make such a fuss?
The two of you already
Does it fit well?
It looks very nice
Yeah?
Oh, if you want to enter into this partnership after all,
It has to fit together well.
Let's guess, then
Is that so?
Baby, if it doesn't work out
Let's try to fit it in, today.
That's right
Even if there is nothing to see
This is my karma
enough
It’s grand, isn’t it? In my eyes
Let's go in
Ah
This bastard
I came to get the money I borrowed
I'm not a gangster
They've been frying the fields since broad daylight, damn it, Mr.
Hey, you got it.
What did you ask me to find out?
What the triad kids say
Eric Choi is behind Mason.
They say it's right
Made by Filipino kids in LA
Looks like he was in a gang.
Are you sure it's him?
I guess it's a captured photo.
I was a little confused at first, but
The same person said it seemed like it was right.
Hey, hey, that's enough
Oh my, I apologize for being rude.
My kids are very suspicious
It's okay
Even at the airport
What is the entry procedure?
Isn't it true?
Let's go
Please sit down.
Wow
Oh, I'll take a look at the building later.
When I tried to do it, what was this...
Because I can see everything at a glance like this
There is no need to look back
I have everything
It should all be in the palm of my hand
I tend to feel relieved.
Well, then
I'm going to get something to drink.
Please share your words
Yeah
Where are you going?
A guest has arrived
Wouldn’t it be wise to get something to drink?
Then
I made the kids do it
I'll tell you to get in
Please stay inside
There is no work
I want to go to my bathroom too
What is that?
Why is it like that all of a sudden?
Hey, Yoo Seung-ah, the camera is out.
Tell the kids to recover quickly.
Well, with Mason
What kind of relationship is this?
Actually, I
living in LA
I know my Filipino friends quite well.
in vulgar language
It was a completely different life.
Then one day
Some fat guy came to see me
work for me
He said why not try it together?
That was Mason
Ah
Written by Mason
That one eye for people is
I think it was awesome
I only use this head
Because it is specialized
I'm really bad at exercising.
That's why I can't throw a breaking ball.
Let me ask you one thing directly:
yes
Mason with me
Can you connect me?
No, you haven't even heard my answer yet.
Aren't you being too hasty?
Wow, this took a big hit.
Okay
So let's change the question.
Do you know Genie Tourism Development?
Recently in Singapore
Constructed the largest integrated resort
Mason there
He wants to scout.
Those words are
Let's hand Mason over to Genie...
Ah, ah
The money that comes from there
Let’s say Eric gets everything.
I just need to get my business license.
How do you feel?
Being in the same boat as me
Ha, well, it's not that difficult.
If I were to be in the same boat, I would
You're investing in me
It seems like a better option
I think about it
Investment?
Ah, this
Isn't it an online casino game?
Are you telling me to invest here now?
The return on investment is
We will definitely guarantee it
unfortunately for each other
It seems like the needs are different, so I'll give it a try.
When speaking nicely
Take a look and think about it.
You won't regret it
who is
Would you like to find out?
Hey, Mr.
Can't you hurry up, can you?
Did you call me?
Now in the machine room
Because I'm fixing the surveillance camera.
In the meantime, be on guard around the kids.
Please make it clearer. Yes, I understand.
Ah, if it is Rep. Seo Jung-geun
Integrated resort at Genie Tourism Development
This is a nobleman who gave permission to build it.
He is also the person who helped me with my business.
Ah, so now that means...
As the CEO said
When you can't throw a breaking ball
Just throw a fastball
think about it
Even if I take Mason to Genie.
Will I be able to get the business license?
I can't guarantee
But the business rights
If it goes through the person holding it
Rep. Seo Jung-geun
- Are you saying you want to connect me?
- As long as you make a decision on the agenda I mentioned earlier.
Is this a problem?
But what is this piece of paper?
It can be manipulated as much as you like.
That's Rep. Seo Jung-geun.
That we know each other
How are you going to prove it?
Proof...
Ah, proof
What's the big deal?
If you are truthful, it will be proven.
Oh, excuse me for a moment.
Yes, Senator, I got the call.
Uh, Eric
Where are you now?
The phone goes back to overseas roaming.
Oh, I'm trying to find a partner right now.
I'm in China for a little while.
I see.
It's nothing else but a public hearing.
It's scheduled.
It happened as you wished.
Really?
The people of our country
Because it's simple
P2E and all?
There is no need for all difficult concepts
In words that just seem to exist
If you just add the ideology of ‘freedom’
You think that’s democracy?
Such an abstract concept
- Oh my, you're coming back quickly.
- Earrings on your ears
If you put it on your nose, it's a nose ring.
- Huh?
- I don't know if I'm being played by politicians.
Are you too busy fighting for sides?
uh?
Uh, oh my god
I think it's done
Then you can take a look at the situation here
CCTV in every room
Make sure it's running properly
yes, i understand
Anyway then
When I meet Chairman Ahn tomorrow,
You can’t come out?
Chairman Ahn?
Hey, instead of me
You can enjoy it.
Ah, thanks Genie
It has been reborn as a global company.
Rep.
You deserve it.
There's something unfamiliar between us
Just let the plane stop
Wow, time flies...
Well, first of all, I'm going to use the congressman's time.
I feel like I took too much
- I will come visit you when I return to Korea, yes.
- The chairman
Please hand over the slush fund account to a borrowed name.
Oh my, are you going to come out like this?
Wait a minute
Hello, congressman.
In Singapore
This is Maseok-gu, preparing for business.
Ah, yes
hello
Ha, are you really Rep. Seo Jung-geun?
That's it
What do you mean?
Oh my, I'm sorry
Oh, it's nothing else
I also participate in Eric’s business.
I was thinking about investing.
I only trust you
Would you trust and invest in a person you have never met?
Isn’t that a too hasty decision?
Yes, I believe you, Senator.
Slush funds in my account
I will invest 5 billion won
I would like to ask you a favor instead.
I need to get a junket business license.
Genie Tourism Development
Please connect me
I understand first of all
Tomorrow at luncheon
Talk closely with Chairman Ahn
I'll bid you farewell
You will probably welcome it without knowing.
casino business
Because I am someone who really wants to grow up.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, thank you, Senator.
I will not forget your grace
They said they would invest in me.
Is there any reason to refuse?
Then, please be kind to me.
Okay, to the congressman.
Representative's email address
I'm trying to send you some.
To the address written on the business card
Can I send it to you?
Of course
That's great, then
Is the investment amount flexible?
Well, what is the form of funding?
Ah, because the purpose is what it is for.
I have it in cryptocurrency now
That would be possible, right?
Of course
It actually got better.
Team leader
What are you doing here?
Ah, that...
I asked what are you doing?
Oh, I have something to look at.
I'll have to check
Please give it to me
Hey, at first this
I thought it wouldn't hit well
Now I see the two of us
I think it could be a match made in heaven.
I guess so
Child, in a past life
I don't know if they were a couple.
Ah, then
Chairman Ahn and Representative Seo
Where do you usually enjoy lunch?
Well, mainly CEO!
Representative!
Let go, let go!
Representative, Representative!
Oh, I'm sorry I broke your colic.
Looks like my child has some urgent business.
Why are you so excited about that?
Come to work, Mr. Let go of this.
What's going on?
This bitch
This is something suspicious
I got caught doing something in the studio.
Even if you tell me to give up cancer, I hug you tight and won’t let you go.
Oh, let go of this!
Can't you let go of this?
CEO
It's really unfair to me
What is it?
before that
Let's just check first.
What confirmation?
Senator, where are you now?
That's right
You must be busy with your general election schedule, right?
Well then, ha
Of course you would like to go to the luncheon tomorrow, right?
Regarding my contract
I'm sure you'll talk well too.
Yes, congressman
You said yes, right?
But that busy man
Why are you in the prosecutor's office?
What do you mean...
Let's hear it
I guess this news was pretty hot today
The one in the center
How could he talk to me leisurely?
Then I
Are you saying it was an impersonation?
Against such a big name?
no
These days, the technology is so good
I'm wondering if that's possible.
you this
You knew everything, right?
Kim Du-sik is all of this
That's what I ordered, everything, huh?
why?
Trying to take it away from me again!
I am
Lee, Mr.
Please stop
‘Would you please stop?’
Then bring the evidence
Congressman Seo in front of me
Bring it to me, now.
Then I'll trust you
Why can't you do it?
customer
not answering the phone
After the beep
Connect to voicemail...
tell me to come right away
When you hear a beep
After recording
I'll give you five hours
Rep.
There's a problem now
I need you to meet me.
Let's meet for more details
I'll tell you
As far as the congressman
You can come out of there for a moment.
Because it’s urgent, by 8pm tonight.
I would like you to come to Seungamsa Temple.
Five hours, Eric.
It's time to return home safely.
- Hey, come in.
- Yes
Put these on the boat
Because I'm going to Korea
yes
Ah, sir!
You don't have much time left
Even after 1 hour
I gave you 5 more minutes.
Why do you keep testing my patience?
uh?
Oh my, Eric
Oh, what on earth is going on?
hello
Eric
What on earth is going on?
That...
somehow
We need to lure Ma Seok-gu to Korea.
There is such a crime prevention
I was arrested right away.
I guess you didn't know
When I was in police academy
I was a reporter for the school newspaper.
It's my hidden card.
Are you asking me to become a daily corrupt politician?
As for me that day
As an investor who has touched some dark money
We'll transform you
Then really
From the IRS
Is your home being searched and seized?
Your wife will be very surprised, right?
When did I meet the congressman?
Have you ever caused trouble?
Oh, that's right
If you help me
Even if it was
I got bullied by these stupid guys.
1 billion intact
When I think of what I gave
I make a thousand dollars at my job
So I told them
I will definitely get rid of it
Will you help me?
No matter what I do
I will cooperate with you
I hope you succeed
yes
Then this story
Only me and the congressman know.
Bondi
When you have a big problem ahead of you
What you need to be most careful about
Because it's the mouth
Are you CEO Ma?
Ah, yes
What kind of situation is this?
Representative Ma, please explain.
Yeah, that...
Rep.
Actually, that's what I...
That
There was some misunderstanding
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
That...
I'm really sorry
I was so blinded by my money that I conspired with Eric.
The investment profits that will be distributed to you, Mr.
I tried to steal it from CEO Ma.
So?
CEO Gramm Ma
Rep. betraying you
They said it would never happen
Be sure to visit me and apologize.
In a fiery rage...
Oh, you foolish person.
Because of that money
Are you trying to betray your trust?
I'm really sorry
Me and the congressman
Representative Ma
Is there a line at the prosecution too?
I went to the prosecution
I planted a person
So that I can be released without charges today.
I'll do my best quickly
All I did was make a phone call.
He's such a trustworthy person.
yes
Ah, yes
thank you
I should repay your faith, right?
Ah, that means...
To Chairman Ahn
Sign a contract with CEO Ma
I'll put my phone away.
Thank you!
Genie Tourism Development
I would have sent an email to CEO Ma.
Please refer to the contract details.
Instead, it was decided to invest once the contract was concluded.
Let's make sure to keep our promise.
What is this?
Mr.
Yes, brother
Hey, back to Seungamsa Temple
take them both away
Yes? No, a little while ago
He told me to take him to Wari Port...
Hey, you bastard
If you pout one more time
I know you'll get dragged in this time
Take me there right away
Ah, yes, I understand.
Oh my, Rep. Seo
I already received the email well.
Representative Ma
Are you going well?
Where is it?
yes, we are going well
Oh, I just crossed Seongan Bridge a little while ago.
yes
Is it okay?
yes? What is it?
Are you still okay?
Oh, what is that...
Thank you, Dojin.
I'm swearing at that person
I thought I was going to die because I was scared.
Didn't I do well though? The acting was good too
Well, the looks aren't bad at this level.
So, I entered the entertainment industry...
Oh my
I hope you come to your senses, Boss Ma, Boss Ma?
Are you seriously injured?
Hey, Mr.
Wi Chang-ok, the bitch that will tear you to death
I will call the police and emergency services immediately.
No way
don't do it
Don't do it, you crazy bitch.
Ah, oops
Boss Ma is wanted now.
I know, right?
Then, if you report it, things will go well.
Could you at least tell it to the chairman?
pair
Can’t you shut that bitch up?
우재요
우재
근데 회장님은 자기 50억이 털린 걸 아나 모르겄소
걱정 마오
그 50억 우리한테 잘 와 있으니
됐어, 됐어
됐어
미안하게 됐소
개다리 노릇 하모 배운 게
이런 거뿐이라
야, 이, 씨
야
너랑 그 새끼, 씨
둘 다 죽여 버릴 거야, 내가
아이고
가따나 아득한 정신에
남 걱정까지 하고 그러오
걱정 마오
그럼
잘 가라, 이 개새끼야
야...
Hey
Hey! Lee, Mr.
Hey! Fuck this
You have to be really careful from now on
They will never stay still.
You know him from earlier, right?
I don't know the face well
Strange tattoo on the neck...
Yesterday near Seongan Bridge
A man went missing?
Missing?
But that man
I think it’s a magic sphere
Even if I find that child
I guess I already have no money.
A real thief
please bring me in front of you
Are you sure it's a magic sphere?
Your life could be in danger
Then why?
I keep circling around you
Park Jeong-hoon!
Where is Maseok-gu in Korea?